Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reference files, 1976-1993; MS2040 Series 3
  - Publications, Margin, 1987-1988 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Margin, 1989 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Mary Jane, undated (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Maryland Poetry Review, 1986-1987 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Mattoid, undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Meanjin, Dec., 1980 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Media Arts, Summer/Fall, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Memphis St. Review, 1981-1987 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Mendocino Review, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Mill, Spring, 1973 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Missing Form, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Missouri Review, Spring, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Publications, The Missouri Review, Summer, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Publications, The Missouri Review, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Publications, MockReviewZ, undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Mondo Hunkamooga, 1983-1984 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Moons and Lion Tails, 1976-1977 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Moose, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Moosehead Review, 1979-1983 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Mosca Group, no date, undated (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Moth, Christmas, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Motheroot Journal, Fall, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Publications, My Life Depends On You, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Nebula 13:, no date, undated (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Publications, MSS Fall/Winter, 1981-1982 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Publications, MSS Spring, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Publications, The Nantucket Review, Spring, 1984 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Nation, 1978-1981 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Negative Capability, Summer Fall, 1985 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Naked Man 6, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Publications, New Anthology, 1978 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Publications, New Art Examiner, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Publications, New Art Examiner, Feb April, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Publications, New Art Examiner, May June, Sept, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Publications, New Art Examiner, Feb March, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Publications, New Asian Writing, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Publications, New Blood, July, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Publications, New England Review, Autumn, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Publications, New Ghent Review, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Publications, New Letters, Fall, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Publications, New Letters, 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Publications, New Mexico Humanities Review, Spring, Summer, Fall, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Publications, New Mexico Humanities Review, 1981-1985 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Publications, New Orleans Review, Summer, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Publications, New Orleans Review, Fall, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Publications, New Orleans Review, Spring/Summer, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Publications, New Pages, 1980-1983 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Publications, New Pages, 1986-1989 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Publications, New Poetry, 1976-1983 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The New Republic, 1981-1982 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Publications, New Valley Press, July Aug., 1981 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The New York Quarterly, Spring Autumn, 1972 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The New York Quarterly, Summer, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Nimrod, Spring, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Publications, 925 ,no. 10 17, undated (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Ninth Decade, 1984-1985 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Nomad, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Publications, The Nonprofit Corporation, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Noospapers, Aug., 1988 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Publications, No Press, 1987-1988 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Normal Man, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Publications, North Dakota Quarterly, Fall, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Publications, North Dakota Quarterly, Spring, Fall, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Publications, North Dakota Quarterly, Summer, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Publications, North Dakota Quarterly, Spring, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Northeast Rising Sun, 1976-1979 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Northwest Review, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Notas, Spring, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Oasis, 1978-1981 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Ocarina, 1978-1979 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Occasional Review, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Ohioana Quarterly, Summer, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Ohio Journal, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Ohio Review, 1980-1983 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Olsosson's Review, 1985-1992 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Publication, One O One, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Publication, Ones, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Publication, On Location, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Publication, Ore, July, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Publication, Oro Madre, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Other Voices, Premier Issue, Winter, 1985-1986 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Other Voices, 1986-1987 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Other Voices, 1987-1988 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Other Voices, 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Outlaw, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Out of Four, 1982 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Out of Sight 75, undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Outre, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Oxalis, 1989-1990 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Publications,The Painted Bride Quarterly, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Publications,The Painted Bride Quarterly, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Palantir, 1979-1982 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Pan American Review, Spring, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Pandemonium Spirit, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Panurge, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Paper Air, 1982-1989 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Paper Air, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Publications,Parabola, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Parallel, nd, undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Parallelogramme, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Parallelogramme, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Parallelogramme, 1982 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Parallelogramme, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Parallelogramme, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Partisan Review, September-October, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Publications, PBM, Spring, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Peau Sensible, Winter, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Penguin Voices, June, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Pen in Hand, 1990-1992 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Pennsylvania Review, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The Pennsylvania Review, 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Pequod, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Periaktus, 1987 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Piddiddle, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Pig in a Pamphlet, nd, undated (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Pig in a Poke, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Pig Iron Magazine, 1978-1982 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Publications, The Pikestaff Review, Summer, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Pinch Penny, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Phantasm, 1980-1981 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Planet Detroit Magazine, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Platform, nd, undated (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Ploughshares, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Poems, 1984 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Poet & Critic, 1984-1985 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Poetic License, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Poetic Space, 1989-1990 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Poet Lore, Spring, 1963 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Poetry as a Positive Dimension, Winter, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Poetry Australia, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Poetry Comics, 1980-1981 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Poetry from Pueblo, nd, undated (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Poetry from Sacramento, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Poetry from Holland and Belgium, 1985 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Poetry Handcards, nd, undated (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Poetry Information, 1977-1978 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Publications, Poetry Ireland, 1985-1986 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Poetry Kanto, Summer, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Poetry Motel 10, 1985-1992 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Poetry News, October, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Poetry Now, 1981-1983 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Poetry Olympics, 1980 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Poetry Pilot, 1984 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Poetry Project Newsletter, April, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Publications, The Poetry Review, April, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Poet's Corner, May, 1985 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Poetry Quarterly, Summer, 1952 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Polis, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Pontchartrain Review, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Portland Assemblage, nd, undated (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Portland Review, Fall, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - Publications, The Pottersfield Portfolio, 1982-1988 (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Poultry: A Magazine of Choice, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Powell's Books, Autumn, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Prairie Fire, 1986 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Prairie Schooner, Spring, 1975 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Preview, May, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Proof Rock, 1984-1986 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Prose Political, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Pub, Spring, 1980 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Publisher's Weekly, 1984-1989 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, Summer, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, 1983 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, 1986-1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, Winter, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, 25th Anniversary Issue, 1988 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, Summer, 1989 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Puerto del Sol, Spring, 1991 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Pulp, January, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Pulpsmith, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Pulpsmith, Winter, 1984 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Quarterly West, Fall, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Quarterly West, Winter, 1987-1988 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Quest, Winter/Spring, 1969 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Radio Void, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Rag Mag, Fall, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Random Weirdness, May, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Ransom, 1988-1989 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Rawbone, 1983-1985 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Real Fiction, nd, undated (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Reality Studios, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Publications, The Reaper, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Recuerdo, Winter, 1959 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Red Bass, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Red and Green, August, 1987 (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Reflections, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Renewing Dialects, 1985 (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Resurgence, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Review, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Revue, 1983-1984 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Rewrite, 1982 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Richmond Boome, 1978-1979 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Richmond Trolleys, 1985 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Rio Grande Writers Newsletter, 1984 (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Publications, River City, 1990 (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Publications, River Rat Review, 1987 (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Publications, River Styx, 1987-1988 (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Roadrunner Bio, nd, undated (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Roberson Poetry Annual, 1980 (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Rock Drill, 1981-1983 (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Routines That Will Kill You, 1993 (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Publications, SABSS, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Salmagundi, 1984 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Salmon, 1984-1986 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Salmon, 1986-1987 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Salthouse, 1975-1983 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Samisdat, 1981-1982 (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Samisdat, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Sandwiches, 1976 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Satori, 1989 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Publications, The Savoy Book, undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Scarab, 1992 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Scopp, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Scrape, 1986 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Scratch 'n Sniff, nd, undated (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Scree, 1978 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Scree, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Scorpion, 1984-1987 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Seattle Review, 1983 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Seattle Review, 1984 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Seattle Review, 1985 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Second Coming, 1980-1981 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Second Coming, 1986 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Second Hand Books, nd, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Seems, 1982 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Seneca Review, 1981 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Sentences, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Separate Door, Spring, 1985 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Sepia, 1978-1979 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Sepia, 1980-1981 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Sepia, 1982-1983 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Sepia, 1984-1988 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The Serendipity Caper, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Shankpainter 29, 1982-1989 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Shattersheet, 1986 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Shearsman, 1981-1982 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Shooting Star, Summer, 1989 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Publications, The Short Story Review, Summer/Spring, 1987 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Publications, A Shout in the Street, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Publications, SHY, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Shraff, nd, undated (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Publications, SIC Biscuit, 1983 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Signal Network International, 1988 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Signal Network International, 1989 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Simbolica, nd, undated (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Simply Thrilled Honey, 1981 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Sipapu, 1980-1983 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Sipapu, 1984-1986 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Sipapu, 1987-1993 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Publications, The Slackwayer Review, nd, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Slipstream, 1983-1987 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Slow Dancer, 1979-1980 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Slow Dancer, 1981-1990 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Small Pet Repair, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Small Press, Sept. Dec., 1983 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Small Press, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Small Press, 1985 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Small Press, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Small Press, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Small Press, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Small Press, 1989-1991 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Small Press Editor's Round Table, nd, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Small Press News, 1981-1985 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Small Press Publishing in Australia by Michael Denholm, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1970-1978 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1979 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1982 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1983 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1986 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1987 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Publications, The Small Press Review, January-May, 1989 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The Smith, 1969-1972 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Smith, 1975-1980 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Smoke, 1976-1980 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Somke, 1982-1984 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Smoke, 1985-1987 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Publications, The Smudge, 1978-1981 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Snappy Stanzas, nd, undated (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Snowy Egret, Autumn, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Sodom Society News, January, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Publications, ndSummer, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Solo, April-May, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Some Footnotes for the Future, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Sonora Review, Fall, 1981 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Sonora Review, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Sonora Review, 1984-1985 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Sonora Review, 1988-1989 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Sonora Review, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Sonora Review, Winter, 1991 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Sore Dove, Fall, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Publications, South Dakota Review, 1984 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Publications, South Dakota Review, 1985-1989 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Publications, South Dakota Review, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Southern Exposure Festival, Summer, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Sow's Ear, Fall, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Sparrow, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Speak Easy, 1982 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Stake, nd, undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Stance, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Stance, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Stand Magazine, 1986-1987 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Stand Magazine, 1987-1988 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Stand Magazine, 1988-1991 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Stand Magazine Autumn, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Stand Magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Star Web Paper, 1960-1971 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Stomp, March, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Stone Drum, Spring, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Publications, The Stone Gargoyle, #1, undated (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Stony Hills, 1977-1983 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Stony Run, Spring, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Stop Breaking Down, August, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Stories, September October, 1982 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Story Quarterly, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Story Quarterly, 19821983 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Story Quarterly, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Story Quarterly, 1985 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Stride, 1984 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Stride, 1984-1985 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Stride, 1987 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1985-1989 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Sulphur River, Autumnal Equinox, 1991 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Summer Salt, nd, undated (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Publications, The Sun, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Publications, The Sun, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Sun, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Sun, 1984-1988 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Swallow's Tale Magazine, Spring, 1983 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Swamp Root, 1988-1989 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Swamp Root, Winter/Spring, 1990 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Swellsville, undated (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Sycamore Review, 1989-1990 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Sydelines, nd, undated (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Tabula Rosa, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Publications, TAK TAK TAK, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Talisman, Spring, 1983 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Tamarind, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Tamarack, Spring-Summer, 1979 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Tangerine, February, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Taproot, February, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Publications, The Tasmanian Review, 1979-1980 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Publications, The Tattered Cover, Spring, 1986 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Publications, undated (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Telegram I, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Tendril, Winter, 1984 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Thelma, Spring, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Publications, A Third Foreign Fazine, May, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Threads of Texas Literature, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Thunder Sandwich, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - Publications, TLR, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Publications, Thursdays, 1987 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Publications, Transnational Perspectives, 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Trends, 1983-1984 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Three Rivers, 1977 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Two Hands News, January, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Publications, 2 Ton Santa, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Type World, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Umbra, 1981 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Umbrella, September, 1983 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Underground Magscene, August-September, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Underground Rag Mag, 1982-1983 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Urbane Gorilla, 1979-1980 (Box 102, Folder 11)
  - Publications, US, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Publications, US 1, 1975-1981 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Vanderbilt Review, Spring, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Vegetable Box, 1980-1982 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Voyages, Winter, 1970 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Publications, The Walrus Said, August, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Washington Independent Writers, 1982-1986 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Washington Post Magazine, August, 1991 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Waves, 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Publications, Waves, 1984-1985 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Publications, Waves, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Publications, Waves, 1986-1987 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Publications, Welter, Spring, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Publications, West Branch, 1977-1980 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Publications, West Branch, 1984-1985 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Publications, West Branch, 1986 (Box 104, Folder 4)